sensedigital.in 2019-06-30

# Privacy Policy | Sense Digital

## PRIVACY POLICY

* * *

#### ABOUT Sense Digital Media Pvt. Ltd. & THE CONTENT OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

**Sense Digital Media Pvt. Ltd. is India's** leading digital media network platform enabling advertisers and marketers across the region to communicate with their audiences and helping publishers to grow their revenues with better optimization and campaign planning.This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

**General Note and Industry Definitions**  
 **Ad Tags:** Ad Tags are pieces of code that allow the delivery of online advertisements in the dedicated ad spaces on websites and in online applications. Ad Tags may transmit certain anonymous information about the web site, section of the site and size of the ad that we are optimizing.  
**API:** An application programming interface or "API" is a particular set of rules and specifications that allows one software program to access and make use of another software program. It helps facilitate the interaction between applications, similar to the way the user interface facilitates interaction between humans and computers.

**Cookies:** Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. Personally Identifiable Information: We define personally identifiable information (or "PII") as "information that can be used to uniquely identify, contact, or locate a single person or can be used with other sources to uniquely identify a single individual." e. g. name, address, social security number, e-mail address etc. PII can be sensitive or non-sensitive. Non-sensitive PII is information that can be transmitted in an unencrypted form without resulting in harm to the individual. Non-sensitive PII can be easily gathered from public records, phone books, corporate directories and websites.

**Real-Time Bidding:** Real-Time Bidding (or "RTB") is a method of buying online or mobile advertising inventory by responding in real-time to an ad call with a "bid," usually priced by cost per thousand impressions ("CPM"), to buy that single impression and thus the opportunity to display an ad to that user. RTB buyers use multiple different data sources, including third parties, to more precisely target the ads they display.

**Web Beacons & Pixels:** A web beacon consists of a small string of code that represents a graphic image request on a web page, a page in an online application, or in an email. A graphic image can be associated with the web beacon, but is not required. When an image is present, usually the image is designed to blend into the background of the web page, application, or email in which it appears. Often a beacon will be placed by an online data collecting company without an image, so it is invisible to the user, and in the smallest discrete space possible on the screen. This is a "pixel" and is essentially an invisible web beacon. Pixels and web beacons can be used for site traffic reporting, unique visitor counts, advertising auditing and reporting, personalization, and other uses. They do this typically by writing or editing cookies on each user's computer. Therefore, like cookies, they cannot be used to key log, copy personal files from your computer, or replicate like a virus. Most pixels and web beacons, including those used us collect only anonymous data. However, some may be used to collect PII, particularly in the case of email that contains a web beacon. In such cases, the data collected through the web beacon may be linked to the recipient's email address or other information identifying the recipient.

**What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**  
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your phone number or other details to help you with your experience.

**When do we collect information?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form or enter information on our site.

**How do we use your information?**  
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To personalize user's experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
  * To improve our website in order to better serve you.
  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To quickly process your transactions.
  * To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.

**How do we protect visitor information?**

  * We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.
  * We use regular Malware Scanning.
  * Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

**Do we use 'cookies'?**  
YES

**We use cookies to:**

  * Keep track of advertisements.
  * Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third party services that track this information on our behalf.
  * You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.
  * If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled It won't affect the users experience that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.

**Third Party Disclosure**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.  
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Google**  
Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en  
We have not enabled Google AdSense on our site but we may do so in the future.

**Users can visit our site anonymously**  
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.  
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy', and can be easily be found on the page specified above.

**Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:**  
On our Privacy Policy Page  
**Users are able to change their personal information:**  
By emailing us

**How does our site handle do not track signals?**  
We honour do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

**Does our site allow third party behavioural tracking?**  
It's also important to note that we allow third party behavioural tracking

**Children Under 13 Years of Age**  
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. We do not specifically market to children under 13.

**Fair Information Practices**  
Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.  
In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur: We will notify the users via email Within 1 business day.  
We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

**CAN SPAM Act**  
The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations. However opt out does not block Ads, Opt-out does not block data collection and Opt-out is browser specific.

**We collect your email address in order to:**

To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:  
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at privacy@sensedigital.in and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.

Contacting Us If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

**sensedigital.in  
417, MGF Metropolis Mall, MG Road  
Gurgaon, India 122002  
India  
privacy@sensedigital.in**
